A Ansari Motiur Rehman G.R

ABOUT ME

React Developer

Since 2017

Started learning JavaScript and its frameworks after my graduation. Started exploring React as hobby and then landed in a job for the same. I am a tech enthusiastic person, who keeps on learning new tech standards and evolving my knowledge.

I have also published **Spell-Out** npm package.

EXPERIENCE

United Software Pvt Ltd

Aug 2017 - Aug 2023 | Software Developer - MERN

- Oreating widgets for sports and news domains.
- Creating dashboards for different clients as per their requirements.

- Actively participate in daily Scrum meeting.

Koshali Arts & Crafts Enterprise

Nov 2023 - Dec 2023 | Full Stack Developer - Remote

- Create and maintain e-commerce related web applications.
- Create reusable components and pages with Next.js.
 Sharing data among components with redux-tool-kit.
- O Designing pages with Material UI and Tailwind CSS.

EDUCATION

A-I Kalsekar Technical Campus

2012 – 2015 | Bechlor's Degree in Engineering (Electronics and Telecommunication)

A-I Kalsekar Polytechnic

2008 – 2011 | Diploma in Engineering - Full time 3 years (Electronics and Telecommunication)

Ideal High School & Jr. College

2007 - 2008 | SSC

PROJECTS

Online Food Delivery Application

Since 2018-2022 | React, Redux, Node, MongoDB

This application is related to booking online food orders. User can see list of food items in given resturants and can book orders. We have used Node & Express as backend and for frontend we used React and Bootstrap. To persist user data we used MongoDB.

Advanced Inventory System

2019 - 2023 | React, Node, MongoDB, ShadCn

Various local mills needs to maintain their paper-based inventory on daily basis, so we digitalized their paper-based inventory system cum human resource management. For user interface we used React along with Material UI, and Node and Express as backend.

SKILLS

MERN Stack

Intermediate Level

HTML5	CSS3	JavaScript	ES7	React	RTK
NextJs	NodeJs	ExpressJs	MongoDB		MySQL

Other

Git	Postman		Bootstrap		o	Material UI		
ShadCn UI Ta			lwind CSS Sty			yled Components		
Srapi CMS		Heroku		Netlify		Python		
Jupyter Notebook								

CONTACT

- ල github.com/ansarimati
- ⊘ kaggle.com/ansarimati
- ⊘ linkedin.com/in/ansarimati
- © Cheeta Camp, Trombay, Mumbai 400088
- ☐ ansari.mati.aiktc@gmail.com
- **&** (+91) 8169-6234-89